
> portfolio@0.1.0 dev
> next dev

笆ｲ Next.js 16.2.9 (Turbopack)
- Local:         http://localhost:3000
- Network:       http://192.168.1.5:3000
笨・Ready in 386ms
Attention: Next.js now collects completely anonymous telemetry regarding usage.
This information is used to shape Next.js' roadmap and prioritize features.
You can learn more, including how to opt-out if you'd not like to participate in this anonymous program, by visiting the following URL:
https://nextjs.org/telemetry


